{
    "id": "0014debb8f364534aa7840fc392a35e6",
    "title": "Identify the adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is clearly something wrong with her.",
            "description": "Adverbs are words that indicate ideas such as time, place, manner and frequency. ",
            "answers": [
                "clearly",
                "wrong",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d609e483f6e481b8eae1d947a9893c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is my teacher but she is also my friend.",
            "description": "But is a conjunction and friend is a noun. Also is the adverb. ",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "friend",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "796a099ce56644788b68bcb53063a236"
        },
        {
            "question": "He always wears a coat, even in summer.",
            "description": "Wears is a verb and summer is a noun. Always is the adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "always",
                "wears",
                "summer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efe21798076042ba975fa7da396a1e52"
        },
        {
            "question": "He often comes and stays with us.",
            "description": "With is a preposition and is a conjunction often is an adverb of frequency",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "often",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fa4e55e0b954bacb35ed8134361f21f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to Venice today.",
            "description": "Time words are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "to",
                "today"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "33b6ce73a4f64f438fbd9897abeb0ce0"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have definitely been a great help.",
            "description": "Words ending in -ly are usually adverbs note that there are a few exceptions to this rule. ",
            "answers": [
                "definitely",
                "been",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e082daccc8447cd9ffb8c6a23ed6d3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time next week, I will be happily working in my garden.",
            "description": "Next is an adjective garden is a noun happily is the adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "next",
                "happily",
                "garden"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0c7b3b86e394289af7f33cfa8ede423"
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t think the repair has been properly done.",
            "description": "Properly is an adverb indicating manner.",
            "answers": [
                "think",
                "repair",
                "properly"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d26041b7cda14db2b9ac4395c68537a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am really sorry for disturbing you.",
            "description": "Really is an adverb indicating manner.",
            "answers": [
                "really",
                "sorry",
                "disturbing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "032435a47a9244c8a6016352b0f019d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went to bed early.",
            "description": "Words indicating time, place, manner, frequency, condition etc., are all adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "went",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca62970a9295460c8d681708b186adaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The war seriously affected oil prices.",
            "description": "Words indicating manner are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "war",
                "seriously",
                "affected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a023dca087a34d14b75d83a9b798343d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She must sometimes have wanted to run away.",
            "description": "Words indicating time and frequency are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "sometimes",
                "run"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5f5b98082174ae299d78b808b163cc8"
        }
    ]
}